<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Daniel Cornock</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
        <description>Personal portfolio page of Daniel Cornock, a front end developer from Birmingham, United Kingdom.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 01:35:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>#100DaysOfCode - My Thoughts So Far</title>
            <link>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/100-days-of-code
            </link>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;If you’re an active member of the tech community, I’d be surprised if you hadn’t heard of #100DaysOfCode. It’s a coding challenge which, as you might have guessed, goes on for 100 days. The rules of the challenge are flexible, with each tailoring it to their own lifestyle. For me, I chose to aim to do an hour of either learning, coding, designing, or blog post writing every day (where ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/100-days-of-code
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>My first post using netlifyCMS!</title>
            <link>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/my-first-post-using-netlifycms
            </link>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;POST RESERVED FOR FUTURE USE&lt;/p&gt;

            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/my-first-post-using-netlifycms
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>The Anatomy of a Website</title>
            <link>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/tutorials/website-anatomy
            </link>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;For newcomers, jumping straight into code can be a daunting task. For somebody that’s been creating websites for a while, the layout of a HTML page might seem simple, or even obvious. This is the curse of knowledge at its peak here, so in this article I will be reverse-engineering a website in ways, so that you can see exactly how it is built, and why it is built the way it is.&lt;/p&g...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/tutorials/website-anatomy
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>CSS Positioning For Absolute Beginners</title>
            <link>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/tutorials/css-positioning
            </link>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;Positioning objects in CSS can often be quite a daunting task. There are 4 main types of positioning, some which you will use all the time! Others, not so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Absolute Positioning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Relative Positioning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed Positioning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sticky Positioning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Static Positioning&lt;...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/tutorials/css-positioning
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hello, and welcome to my humble blog!</title>
            <link>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/my-first-post
            </link>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;Hi, and welcome to my web development blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, you can find my thoughts, ideas and experiences within the web development world. I will also be posting tutorials for common development concepts, both to help others and for my own benefit when I need a little bit of a reminder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you find something here that can benefit you or you ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/blog/discussion/my-first-post
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>